that's great what up scope ease do we
have scope is f11 scope ed3 scope is six
copies so T's copy
pfft damn fast
Thanks
we were just talking about friend texted
me saying uh turns out that a BMW you
know and some other company are
investigating blockchain technology for
automotive and they've partnered with
iota it's crazy
okay guys wait is this common knowledge
so I'm gonna turn to Lansky oh whoa whoa
open the little lock you really want to
make him which could have done landscape
for the beginning I know they like it
yeah now we're gonna do it we're gonna
do it maybe people like because I can't
get ya
yeah yeah it's kind of weird
io does fake news dude okay honestly so
dumb um iota rolled their own crypto
it's a centralized thing tangles do not
work but this is an example of what's
wrong with like the world the fact that
like something like iota first super
hard Josh I'll thank you
the fact that's something like iota like
I don't know what you have to give iota
is they do have the best shells like we
get tweeted at maybe like you know once
a week for someone like if you consider
blockchain okay you can say what you
want about blockchain you know I'm a fan
of Bitcoin with etherium
Roger Miret tried to save it oh I saw
that actually yeah 600 million people
are six hundred people on Twitter were
like sell your Bitcoin cash
[Music]
does not comma that was asking with the
meaning of life you let us know
difference we're still trying to figure
it out so now you guys know what the
meaning of life is to win you can
interpret that to mean that was
something that was balanced out but that
was not good Oh Lane was weird well
Amy's here yeah go get the new waters
let's see any models
yeah what do you do like what do you do
what you do why do you do what you do I
think I might have missed the turnoff
did I miss the turnoff to 101 I don't
know if it's coping Oh put it in our
little ways ya know if I miss the
turnoff
no no we'll never get back figure it out
before it's too late why don't we use
this system how we gonna get all the way
over to Fremont to go to Fremont
Cadillac - but I had GM with Supergirl
oh damn ah
Fremont Fremont George always gets
distracted when scoping and driving I'm
not distracted am i distracted no you're
very you're very if we had everything
you'd be doing fine good things okay can
anyone read this I think might want to
try to get over here let's try
while we're exploring let's go to Milly
brain we've been on this exit either way
so ago and we got his because we
couldn't pair the phones and answer the
phone to the Civic and so we got off
this exit and pulled over to try to
parent remember yeah and then it was
like a weird sketchy road I could be
wrong but I thinks
where are we going to Millie bright
Millbrae Millbrae okay that a Cal Tran
there they do they do
oh no wait that's not what should we
just go back let's do it let's explore
Millie break
Oh milk raise a lovely place we've been
here have we yeah I really don't think
I've ever been here but I know we have
when well I definitely think I thought I
was here with you and we were trying to
go again come on we're trying to go to
melody Toyota we all right we're not
going to melody Toyota guys all right so
we have to get to over there yes all
right well let's go I have a Civic yeah
they're really good though I think
that's about how much is it apart
why is your light on you're right thank
you
yeah bottle for swarthy wasn't yeah that
was not great I can't believe that light
was a good point
I know
but yo guys what El Camino Real
private congratulations I got Mary know
he's finishing the last question of his
last final of his last class until
graduation
Wow boom College is important college
support wait are you lost
it's not a through Street dude look
where we are in the map or nowhere but
nowhere nothing no comma this is the
suburbs one day we'll have a good
self-driving car in the suburbs I won't
date last night guys
yeah tell us about this girls kind of
mind-blowing no are you no but I think
she hates be excited so you're totally
in love that's right that's the best one
I don't think so I don't think I think
Jackie you thinks I'm a bad influence on
our life
oh geez that's real yeah it's not okay
to be about it yeah drop out man turn on
tune in drop out right
scope EEP it is done don't take us far
as that girl the girl from last night
my god she's watching she's watching
tell her I'm in love with her I'd love
to see her again
but she
No if this isn't go anywhere
I mean I'm as lost as you are we're
nothing but I'm just trying to follow
this and I don't know why we're now like
that way we are literally so long
they're so lost how do we get lost on
the way to mili braces so we're not even
going to mill mili Bray we just said I
was that way yeah right no it does the
ocean let's get to the ocean that's very
good haha what's my role I run
operations maybe you should use Waze
don't y'all have navigation no no this
is the point of life you guys asked
we're bringing you through that's right
welcome scope ease you think you have
navigation and but you don't and you're
lost you need comment you see maps not
get lost I've kind of edge the maps that
would be driving right now check out our
positions page check out our hiring page
yeah
this makes the scope 10 times more fun
what makes the scope to attach my fun
though we got lost
don't you get lost distracted you guys
oh it's that it's sad that people think
that that's what it is to be on drugs
like have excitement you know guys no
honestly though like we don't want drugs
some more normal not what I'm not
smoking wheezing yeah that's right man
telling us was more saving he's ever
been yeah and then that guy who was
interviewing him it was like I'm gonna
therapy every Thursday because sometimes
I feel like graffiti from The Lion King
something like that it was dope
scobie's if you haven't checked it out
the Kanye West to Young's the interview
is gold
this leg stand it up and like he's
talking with two people in the newsroom
by the end of the interview the whole
newsroom is quiet and listening to him
talk oh really
wait did he bleach his hair did he
bleach his hair I think if I saw the I
think he bleed she's fair yeah okay well
we got train tracks in the way how we
get over the train tracks really tried
oh that's tight
damn homie oh don't worry if I hit that
minivan it's all the improvement yeah
and maybe a full coverage on our car oh
yeah let's do it really we got a special
Pacific demolition derby okay right no
but seriously I gotta go to the other
side of those train tracks
Oh forever we should use the map says
it's good to know and yes that's what I
heard that's why there's a million oh
that's like the one thing the problem
with these suburbs soon as you feel like
you've been in the same place for 15
minutes beautiful baseball yeah that's
really nice the only kids go outside
anymore - so probably more no no they
don't
nor do they let them eat romaine lettuce
really hurt yeah is there a problem of
lettuce yeah there's a problem with
lettuce
what's wrong with us some kind of
disease oh you gotta watch out you gotta
be safe yeah the usual
no but seriously you should not be
buying lettuce from your local grocery
store unless they like
why do you believe the news and it's all
frayed with lettuce it's not a bad thing
to believe right it's not like they made
a big seller
[Music]
Cole go I heard Taco Bell had that no
fully closed off man I get my Mexican
fast food mixed up we're back folks
comma Papa Murphy's have a Murphy's what
is that Papa Murphy's I went when I was
in Chico with Chico bruh
oh it's like a pizza place Oh Papa
Murphy's Murphy's kind of like Papa
John's little isn't Papa John's like
racist or something are we not allowed
to support that's what I heard
do you like Papa John like lose it or
something I thought um I mean are we not
allowed to support Papa John's anymore
oh you're right Papa John's Papa John we
can't support them that's right we also
can't support KFC there any
chick-fil-a's around here I can feel
like over tick bliss yes for chick-fil-a
all of it
they're good you ready yeah it's good
and they don't come with mail oh that's
the best thing about chick-fil-a wow it
is just like a chicken sandwich right so
[Music]
I don't have never been nobody to Jersey
dude and the first time to
jack-in-the-boxes we did that route oh
I'm sorry jackin the-box is disgusting
ever tell you about jackin the-box
wrongs meanwhile I'll never go there no
yo man one night and I was like you know
what I want right now check about food
and there was a jack-in-the-box
I wasn't that picky right so you guys
never realize that I really want food
they had like the orange smoothie a
check of us their orange cream so that's
just like for ticktick no Josh barro so
it was a glass in the picture yeah one
of those amazing okay no it didn't come
out this oh oh what do you think
happened I think it wasn't in the glass
no I carried a paper cup yeah yeah yeah
shit this falls out of time use a bait
and switch did you ask for to go wat one
of those and I didn't get that and I've
never you know except for that time in
Vegas where I probably protest up and
said I didn't want to go haven't been
back to a jack-in-the-box sense damn
don't go to Jack in the Box Wow all
because of that you know like cut one
small thing man I mean the world is
small sure someone from Jack's box well
I'm not even gonna say we have a deal I
think we're gonna do it guerilla style I
think we're gonna get a bunch of guys
dressed up in Pampa suits outside of
Panda Express and sell common AI pandas
and every panda purchase comes with a
five-dollar Panda Express gift card
Ram marketing budget all right we gotta
go left here I think this takes us to
the highway yeah that's kind of fun
really good penalty they do yeah they do
by the pie wall yeah delicious oh that
wasn't really fun for the people or
people Union City the reason we went
although the people yeah we robbed some
people yeah we're gonna take the bed to
thank the bag that's right
if it fits were taking the bag this
looks like you go somewhere that's a
chevron you know I got gas that one's at
a Kia Soul resource cop he's watching
this I like pious Souls they're kind of
fun what's that it looks so sketchy I
think it should be an abandoned town and
it's the only thing open
yeah maybe coffee's gone cause
everything else
ghost towns are weird I really set set a
good scene for the American War
Millbrae look at this little bridge
that's sweet the transit hub didn't
sweet wait you know we should rename the
George Washington Bridge that's right
I'm assuming you want to keep the George
card so we just got to find a good last
name for it no I think George can go
George can go I mean maybe we just get
rid of them just bridge just the bridge
the bridge not even live dog there's
like an Apple product not the iPhone
just iPhones bridge the iPhone the
Street Bridge bridge near a Brad it's
all a DAT that sign yo love my life
Jackie and I we did this trip we walked
along like that was like a highway like
this we just saw all of my I love all
yeah yeah Erica is the greatest country
in the world there's so much opportunity
in America you could open a Panera Bread
you could open a jack-in-the-box you
could open in McDonald's mmm
yeah but you can't paint your McDonald's
purple and that's the bubble whoa whoa
yeah they got franchise rules we got us
down you know freedom is freedom until
you you know realize maybe we can paint
it purple you gotta have some like a
freakazoid I'm huge freedom fan but like
but you want to go to a purple
mcdonnell's that my dad was the
McDonald's breeze I wouldn't go to a
purple one but I would go to
well they started doing green McDonald's
you know for people to get into that
health mindset you know I would go to a
blue McDonald's like look at that our
cosine if there was McDonald's with that
sign I'm gonna in and out where is the
internet I was problem
that's why there are bears up low
McDonald's in New Mexico yo let's go to
Mexico and really I'm so there
let's just go yeah dad wait let's get
our super cruise catalog first
self-driving civic say this no problem
no problem
munches are the best part of getting
high yeah you know I hear the food
industry did really well with
legalization Colorado
yeah
it's fine
I'm still 54 loyal people
no that's driving your low-power mode
Oh No not have a charger no I don't
think so they were done and that was
today's scoping and you gotta have
enough power to be able to KBB it kelly
blue that's right yeah didn't bring my
negotiating papers shit
Oh we'll just have to turn around turn
around come back
let's go right back to Melbourne yeah
yeah yeah could have been here so long
ago
[Music]
we tried to go to the unit now we saw
the other side we didn't even try it be
like decided really shit it's really
about the middle of Dumbarton bridge
definitely middle of bridge bridge no no
they can't be bridged dumped what was it
jump Bart and that's an okay babe I
think dumb pardon don't fart yeah that's
not bad yeah you set up pretty good
success right don't barn bridge all
rights go peace we're gonna leave you